Guilherme Baracat Uemura

Magento/Shopify/Big Commerce/Wordpress Developer | baracat@gmail.com

About Me

As a developer, I worked at institutions like Microsoft, Isobar, Ogilvy among others creating website and advertising for Fiat, Jeep, Fiat Chrysler Automobiles, Rio 2016 Olympic Committee, Bunge Foods. I have knowledge in PHP, MySQL, Wordpress, HTML, CSS, LESS, SASS, experience with JQuery, Angular, Vue and other Javascript library.

Experience

Magento developer at Redstage

January 2019

Creating and developing virtual stores in Magento on Redstage.

Front-end developer at Microsoft/Isobar

May 2016 - August 2016 (4 months)

I worked at the Front-End Development team at the official Rio 2016 Olympics website.

PHP | Wordpress developer at Esfera Br Mídia

February 2015 - February 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Creating and developing blogs, websites, Json web server and Apps development.

Front-end developer at Isobar

August 2014 - January 2015 (6 months)

Developer front-end for Fiat and Jeep, I worked with HTML, LESS and SASS, Gulp and Grunt, JavaScript, jQuey and Angular JS

PHP | JS | Wordpress | Front-end developer at Presença Online

May 2014 - August 2014 (4 months)

Creating and developing blogs, websites, Json web server and Apps development.

Front-end developer at Zaboo!

September 2013 - May 2014 (9 months)

Zaboo! was a star-up search for building materials, we used the MVC Framework Codelgniter. I was responsible for all HTML, CSS and JavaScript development.

Web Developer at Brancozulu

December 2008 - September 2012 (3 years 10 months)

Responsible for the creation and development of website (wordpress + adobe flash), blogs, interactive multimedia, animation and advertising campaigns.

Web Developer at Ogilvy Brasil - F.A.V

April 2008 - November 2008 (8 months)

Responsible for website development (adobe flash) for the housing market.

Education

Universidade Estadual de Londrina

Bachelor Degree in Industrial Design, Visual Programming, 2001 - 2005

E.T.E Dr. Adail Nunes de Sousa

Technical Data Processing, Data Processing, 1993 - 1996

Skills

- Magento
- Wordpress
- Front-end
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- PHP
- jQuery
- SEO
- Web Development
- Sass/less
- Gulp

- Shopify
- Big Commerce
- After Effects
- Motion Graphics
- Angular
- VUE.js
- GIT
- Photoshop
- Premiere
- Illustrator
- Google Ads
- PhoneGap

Languages

- Portuguese advanced
- English advanced

- Japanese basic conversation
- **Spanish** basic read and conversation